[{"instructions":"Let's define a new operation +<sub>6</sub>. This operation will give us a way of combining two of the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5 to get another one of them back. To perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result. (That's why the operation is called +<sub>6</sub>.) <br /><br />For example, 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2, because 3 + 5 = 8, and 8 is bigger than 6, so we subtract 6, and 8 - 6 = 2. So 3 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 2.<br /><br />Similarly, 1 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5, because 1 + 4 = 5, and 5 is less than 6 so we leave it alone.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":40526,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":1,"time_elapsed":302936,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Do you see how +<sub>6</sub> works? By subtracting 6 every time we get above 5, we ensure th at when  we combine two numbers using +<sub>6</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 5.<br /><br />Click Continue when you're ready to move on.","rt":65333,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":2,"time_elapsed":368270,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now try one on your own! What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":11276,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":3,"time_elapsed":379547,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 3 because 4 + 5 = 9 and 9 - 6 = 3.","rt":2126,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":4,"time_elapsed":381674,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4886,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":5,"time_elapsed":386560,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 5 because 3 + 2 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":1111,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":6,"time_elapsed":387672,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get you r result .)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":23117,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":7,"time_elapsed":410791,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0 because 1 + 5 = 6 and 6 - 6 = 0.","rt":1196,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":8,"time_elapsed":411987,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4588,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":9,"time_elapsed":416575,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1  = 2 beca use 1 + 1 = 2 and 2 is less than 6.","rt":1218,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":10,"time_elapsed":417793,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":5068,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":11,"time_elapsed":422861,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 3 because 3 + 0 = 3 and 3 is less than 6.","rt":956,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":12,"time_elapsed":423817,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with th e first  number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":4579,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":13,"time_elapsed":428396,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 2 because 4 + 4 = 8 and 8 - 6 = 2.","rt":1160,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":14,"time_elapsed":429557,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":4452,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":15,"time_elapsed":434010,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 1 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 4 because 1 + 3 = 4 and 4 is less than 6.","rt":1004,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":16,"time_elapsed":435014,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":4302,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":17,"time_elapsed":439316,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 1 because 4 + 3 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1137,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":18,"time_elapsed":440454,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, you subtract 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":4081,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":19,"time_elapsed":444535,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 5 because 0 + 5 = 5 and 5 is less than 6.","rt":907,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":20,"time_elapsed":445443,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"question":"What is 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5? <br /><br /> (Remember, to perform +<sub>6</sub>, you start with the first number, and then add the second one to it. If the sum is smaller than 6, that's your result. If the sum is 6 or bigger, yo u subtra ct 6 to get your result.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":3415,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":21,"time_elapsed":448859,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 2 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 1 because 2 + 5 = 7 and 7 - 6 = 1.","rt":1083,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":22,"time_elapsed":449943,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.3-0"},{"instructions":"Now we're going to discuss a couple special properties of this new operation, +<sub>6</sub> that we've learned. First, notice that the number 0 behaves in a special way under +<sub>6</sub>. Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back. We'll say that 0 is the <i>identity</i> under +<sub>6</sub>, because when you combine it with something it gives you that identical thing back.","rt":50142,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":23,"time_elapsed":500088,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"Now that we know 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>, we're going to make a new definition. We'll say that the <i>inverse</i> of a number is the element that you combine with it to produce the identity. For example, 5 +<sub>6</sub> 1 = 0, so we say 1 is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>6</sub>, (remember 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>). Similarly, 3 is its own inverse under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0.","rt":43079,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":24,"time_elapsed":543167,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! What is the inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"10","response_history":["10"],"rt":164789,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":25,"time_elapsed":707957,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 4 under +<sub>6</sub> is 2 because 4 +<sub>6</sub> 2 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":36299,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":26,"time_elapsed":744257,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"5","response":"5","response_history":["5"],"rt":6602,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":27,"time_elapsed":750859,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 1 under +<sub>6</sub> is 5 because 1 +<sub>6</sub> 5 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1049,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":28,"time_elapsed":751908,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":6142,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":29,"time_elapsed":758051,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 3 under +<sub>6</sub> is 3 because 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":903,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":30,"time_elapsed":758955,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":3216,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":31,"time_elapsed":762171,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! The inverse of 2 under +<sub>6</sub> is 4 because 2 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":1357,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":32,"time_elapsed":763529,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, the inverse of an element is the thing which you combine with it to produce the identity.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":4617,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":33,"time_elapsed":768146,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that was incorrect. The inverse of 0 under +<sub>6</sub> is 0 because 0 +<sub>6</sub> 0 = 0, and 0 is the identity under +<sub>6</sub>.","rt":12059,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":34,"time_elapsed":780206,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.7-0"},{"instructions":"It is also possible to successively apply +<sub>6</sub>, and the operation can simply be performed starting with the left-most pair. For example, 2 +<sub>6</sub> 3 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 4 = 3.","rt":27479,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":35,"time_elapsed":807686,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"instructions":"We have one last definition to learn today, using the successive operations we just learned. Let's start with an example. Under our operation +<sub>6</sub> we can make every other number using just 1: 2 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 3 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 4 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, 5 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1, and 0 = 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1 +<sub>6</sub> 1. Because 1 can make every other element under +<sub>6</sub>, we say that 1 is a <i>generator</i> unde r +<sub> 6</sub>. <br /><br /> However, 2 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, and 0 = 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2 +<sub>6</sub> 2, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 2.","rt":84495,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":36,"time_elapsed":892182,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Now you try! Is 3 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":16078,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":37,"time_elapsed":908260,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 3 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 3 = 3, 0 = 3 +<sub>6</sub> 3, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 4, or 5 using just 3.","rt":4418,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":38,"time_elapsed":912679,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"Yes","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":5581,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":39,"time_elapsed":918260,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Sorry, that's incorrect. 5 is a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 5 = 5, 4 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 3 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 2 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, 1 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, and 0 = 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5 +<sub>6</sub> 5, so you can make all of the numbers under +<sub>6</sub> using 5","rt":26637,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":40,"time_elapsed":944897,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"I s 4 a ge nerator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":77298,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":41,"time_elapsed":1022195,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 4 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 4 = 4, 2 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, and 0 = 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4 +<sub>6</sub> 4, but there is no way to make 1, 3, or 5 using just 4.","rt":1178,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":42,"time_elapsed":1023374,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"question":"Is 0 a generator under +<sub>6</sub>? <br /><br /> (Remember, a generator is an element which can make every other element.)","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Yes","No"],"correct_response":"No","response":"No","response_history":["No"],"rt":12573,"trial_type":"questi on","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":43,"time_elapsed":1035948,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 0 is not a generator under +<sub>6</sub>, because 0 = 0, but there is no way to make 1, 2, 3, 4, or 5 using just 0.","rt":1013,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":44,"time_elapsed":1036962,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.10-0"},{"instructions":"Now we are going to ask you some questions about a new operation, +<sub>9</sub>, on the numbers 0, 1, 2, 3, 4, 5, 6, 7, 8. It works exactly like +<sub>6</sub>, except now after adding the two numbers you subtract 9 if your result is 9 or greater. <br /><br />Do you see how +<sub>9</sub> works just like +<sub>6</sub>? By subtracting 9 every time we get above 8, we ensure that when we combine two numbers using +<sub>9</sub>, we only produce numbers between 0 and 8.<br /><br />We'll give you one practice question with feedback to make sure you understand the new operation. After that, try to complete the rema ining qu estions as accurately as possible.","rt":53003,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":45,"time_elapsed":1089965,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"Practice: What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"1","response":"1","response_history":["1"],"rt":7246,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":46,"time_elapsed":1097212,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"feedback":"Correct! 5 +<sub>9</sub> 5 = 1 because 5 + 5 = 10 and 10 - 9 = 1.","rt":948,"trial_type":"feedback","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":47,"time_elapsed":1098160,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 3 +<sub>9</sub> 3?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"6","response":"6","response_history":["6"],"rt":6923,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":48,"time_elapsed":1105083,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 7 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":" free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"2","response":"2","response_history":["2"],"rt":20090,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":49,"time_elapsed":1125174,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 1 +<sub>9</sub> 8?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":6727,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":50,"time_elapsed":1131902,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 5 +<sub>9</sub> 4?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0","response_history":["0"],"rt":7586,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":51,"time_elapsed":1139489,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 6 +<sub>9</sub> 6?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"3","response":"3","response_history":["3"],"rt":9724,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":52,"time_elapsed":1149214,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 4 +<sub>9</sub> 1? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"5, because 4 + 1 = 5, which is below 9.","response_history":["5, becuase ","5, becuase","5, becuas","5, becua","5, becu","5, bec","5, because 4 + 1 = 5, which is below 9."],"rt":27652,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":53,"time_elapsed":1176866,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is 8 +<sub>9</sub> 4? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"3, because 8 + 4 = 12 - 9 = 3","response_history":["3, because 8 + 4 = 12 - 9 = 3"],"rt":22855,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":54,"time_elapsed":1199721,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the identity under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in wor ds how y ou got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"0, because when we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back","response_history":["0, because ","0, Whenever we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back","0, becombine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back","0, becacombine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back","0, becaucombine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back","0, becauscombine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back","0, becausecombine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back","0, because combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back","0, because wcombine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back","0, because whecombine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back","0, because whencombine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back","0, because when combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing  back","0 , because when wecombine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back","0, because when we combine 0 with anything else, we get that same thing back"],"rt":184136,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":55,"time_elapsed":1383858,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 5 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"4","response":"4","response_history":["4"],"rt":35294,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":56,"time_elapsed":1419153,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 2 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"7","response":"7","response_history":["7"],"rt":4346,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":57,"time_elapsed":1423500,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 0 under +<sub>9</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"0","response":"9","response_history":["9"],"rt":5185,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":58,"time_elapsed":1428685,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"What is the inverse of 3 under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"6, because 6 + 3 = 9 = 0","response_history":["6, because 6 + 3 = 9 = 0"],"rt":27774,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":59,"time_elapsed":1456460,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 2 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because there is no way to make 2. 2 +9 2 +9 2 +9 2 +9 2 = 1, 2 +9 2 +9 2 +9 2 +9 2 +9 2 = 3","response_history":["No, because there is no way to make 2. 2","No, because there is no way to make 2. 2 +9 2 +9 2 +9 +9","No, because th ere is n o way to make 2. 2 +9 2 +9 2 +9 +","No, because there is no way to make 2. 2 +9 2 +9 2 +9 2 +9 2 = 1, 2 +9 2 +9 2 +9 2 +9 2 2 +9 2 +9 2 +9 2 +9 2","No, because there is no way to make 2. 2 +9 2 +9 2 +9 2 +9 2 = 1, 2 +9 2 +9 2 +9 2 +9 2 +9 2 = 3"],"rt":277581,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":60,"time_elapsed":1734042,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 3 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"The same as the previous answer, there is no way to make 2. ","response_history":["No, there is no way to make ","The same as the previous answer, there is no way to make 2. "],"rt":50118,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":61,"time_elapsed":1784160,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 5 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Unless I am misunderstanding generators, I can't see how practically any number would be a generator under 9.","response_history":["Unless I am misunderstanding generators","Unless I am misunderstanding generators, I can't see how practically any number would be a generator under 9."],"rt":85236,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":62,"time_elapsed":1869397,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"question":"Is 6 a generator under +<sub>9</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"No, because you cannot make 0,1,2","response_history":["No, because you cannot make 0,1,2,3","No, because you cannot make 0,1,2,","No, because you cannot make 0,1,2"],"rt":39649,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":63,"time_elapsed":1909046,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.12-0"},{"instructions":"Now we'd like to ask you some q uestions  about +<sub>n</sub>, where n could be any postive counting number. For example, n could be 3, or n could be any other counting number you can think of. If you need to write the operation, you can use +_n, and your answers can include n to stand in for the arbitrary value if necessary.","rt":88192,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":64,"time_elapsed":1997239,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of 1 under +<sub>n</sub>?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-1","response":"6, because 1 +6 +n (6) = 0","response_history":["This is get","1 + +_n ","6, because 1 _","6, because 1 + +n","6, because 1 +6 +n (6) = 0"],"rt":189584,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":65,"time_elapsed":2186826,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"What is the formula for the inverse of an element x under +<sub>n</sub>? Please explain in words how you got your answer.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"n-x","response":"I am sorry, I am totally unsure how to answer. I have put a lot of time into this HIT, and I hope this doesn't effect my approval. I am genuinely trying my hardest.","response_history":["I am sorry, I am totally unaware","I am sorry, I am totally unaw","I am sorry, I am totally una","I am sorry, I am totally un","I am sorry, I am totally u","I am sorry, I am totally unsure how to answer. I have put a lot of time into this HIT, and I hope this doesn't effect my approval. I am geuinely trying t","I am sorry, I am totally unsure how to answer. I have put a lot of time into this HIT, and I hope this doesn't effect my approval. I am geuinely trying my hardest.","I am sorry, I am totally unsure how to answer. I have put a lot of time into this HIT, and I hope this doesn't effect my approval. I am genuinely trying my hardest."],"rt":65470,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":66,"time_elapsed":2252297,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"Is there a pattern to which elements are generators? How can you know if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub> without seeing whether it can make all the elements?.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I believe generators are pretty much the same under any scenario, so no matter what 1 will be a generator without knowing any other element.","response_history":["I believe generators are pretty much the same under any scenario. ","I believe generators are pretty much the same under any scenario.","I believe generators are pretty much the same under any scenario. ","I believe generators are pretty much the same under any scenario.","I believe generators are pretty much the same under any scenario, such ","I believe generators are pretty much the same under any scenario, such","I believe generators are pretty much the same under any scenario, suc","I believe generators are pre tty much  the same under any scenario, su","I believe generators are pretty much the same under any scenario, s","I believe generators are pretty much the same under any scenario, so no matter what 1 will be a genenator without knowing any other element.","I believe generators are pretty much the same under any scenario, so no matter what 1 will be a generator without knowing any other element."],"rt":71976,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":67,"time_elapsed":2324274,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an odd number, it must be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"False","response_history":["True","False"],"rt":65659,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":68,"time_elapsed":2389934,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is an even number, it must not be a generator under +<sub>n</sub>.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":7554,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":69,"time_elapsed":2397489,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a divisor of n, that is, x must divide n evenly, with no remainder.","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["True","False"],"correct_response":"False","response":"True","response_history":["True"],"rt":14726,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":70,"time_elapsed":2412215,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"True or false: If x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, x must be a multiple of a divisor of n. Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"True","response":"It depends on what X is, if it's 1 it is a generator and if it's 2 it  isn","response_history":["Bec","Be","B","Because if ","It depends on what X is, if it's 2","It depends on what X is, if it's 1 it is a generator and if it's 2 it isn"],"rt":110907,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":71,"time_elapsed":2523123,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is its inverse a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Always","response":"Sometimes","response_history":["Sometimes"],"rt":28871,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":72,"time_elapsed":2551996,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"if an element x is a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never? Please explain in words why your answer is correct.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"som etimes","response":"Again, depending on what X is, undoubtedly sometime its inverse will be a generator. ","response_history":["Again, depending on what X is, undoubtably sometime i'","Again, depending on what X is, undoubtably sometime its inverse will be a generator. ","Again, depending on what X is, undoubtedly sometime its inverse will be a generator. "],"rt":22209,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":73,"time_elapsed":2574205,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"question":"If an element x is not a generator under +<sub>n</sub>, is x +<sub>n</sub> x a generator under +<sub>n</sub> always, sometimes, or never?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Always","Sometimes","Never"],"correct_response":"Never","response":"Never","response_history":["Never"],"rt":27829,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":74,"time_elapsed":2602035,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.14-0"},{"instructions":"We would like to ask you some questions about your backgro und. Ple ase press Continue to continue.","rt":4391,"trial_type":"instructions","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":75,"time_elapsed":2606427,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your age?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"19","response_history":["19"],"rt":3015,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":76,"time_elapsed":2609443,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your level of education?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Did not graduate high school","High school diploma","Some college, no degree","Associates Degree","Bachelors Degree","Some graduate school, no degree","Masters Degree","Doctorate, M.D., etc."],"correct_response":"","response":"Some college, no degree","response_history":["Some college, no degree"],"rt":2666,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":77,"time_elapsed":2612109,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is the most  advance d math class you've completed? If you have multiple classes and you're not sure which one is most advanced, please list them.","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"Probably AP Calc because I never completed the college math course because of a job opportunity. ","response_history":["Every class in gh","Every class in g","Every class in high school, I never","Every class in high school, I neve","Every class in high school, I nev","Every class in high school, I ne","Every class in high school, I n","Every class in high school, I ","Every class in high school, I","Every class in high school, because of a job oop","Every class in high school, because of a job oo","Every class in high school, because of a job opportunity I never finished any in college. ","proa","pro","pr","p","Probably AP Calc because I never completed college","Probably AP Calc because I never completed colleg","Probably AP Calc because I never completed colle","Probabl y AP Cal c because I never completed coll","Probably AP Calc because I never completed col","Probably AP Calc because I never completed co","Probably AP Calc because I never completed c","Probably AP Calc because I never completed the college math course because of a job oop","Probably AP Calc because I never completed the college math course because of a job oo","Probably AP Calc because I never completed the college math course because of a job opportunity. "],"rt":135839,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":78,"time_elapsed":2747948,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of modular arithmetic?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","response_history":["2 -  heard of it but didn't know what it was"],"rt":24143,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":79,"time_elapsed":2772091,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"How familiar are you with the concept of a mathematical group?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - never heard of it","2 - heard of it but didn't know what it was","3 - seen it used or explained","4 - used it but not often or recently","5 - used it, remember and understand it"],"correct_response":"1","response":"1 - never heard of it","response_history":["1 - never heard of it"],"rt":30365,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":80,"time_elapsed":2802456,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you learned something from this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3855,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":81,"time_elapsed":2806312,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you feel you understood the concepts in this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":3041,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":82,"time_elapsed":2809353,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you enjoy this HIT?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["1 - not at all","2 - somewhat","3 - definitely"],"correct_response":"1","response":"2 - somewhat","response_history":["2 - somewhat"],"rt":2568,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":83,"time_elapsed":2811922,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is your gender?","response_type":"multi","response_choices":["Female","Male","Other"],"correct_response":"","response":"Male","response_history":["Male"],"rt":1755,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":84,"time_elapsed":2813677,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"What is/are your native language(s)? (The languages spoken in your household when you were a child.)","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"English","response_history":["English"],"rt":7411,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":85,"time_elapsed":2821089,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Did you use pen and paper at any point on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I used my computer notebook, so sort of.","response_history":["N","I used my computer notebook, so sort of."],"rt":14503,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":86,"time_elapsed":2835593,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"},{"question":"Do you have any comments on this HIT?","response_type":"free","response_choices":[],"correct_response":"","response":"I tried  my best, this got pretty complicated over my head towards the end and I was never good at math to begin with. I was never bored throughout this hit, and it was definitely one of the most interesting of any I have taken. ","response_history":["I tried my best, this got pretty complicated over my head towards the end and I was never good at bath ","I tried my best, this got pretty complicated over my head towards the end and I was never good at bath","I tried my best, this got pretty complicated over my head towards the end and I was never good at bat","I tried my best, this got pretty complicated over my head towards the end and I was never good at ba","I tried my best, this got pretty complicated over my head towards the end and I was never good at bm","I tried my best, this got pretty complicated over my head towards the end and I was never good at b","I tried my best, this got pretty complicated over my head towards the end and I was never good at math to begin with. I wa s never  bored though out ","I tried my best, this got pretty complicated over my head towards the end and I was never good at math to begin with. I was never bored though out","I tried my best, this got pretty complicated over my head towards the end and I was never good at math to begin with. I was never bored though ou","I tried my best, this got pretty complicated over my head towards the end and I was never good at math to begin with. I was never bored though o","I tried my best, this got pretty complicated over my head towards the end and I was never good at math to begin with. I was never bored though ","I tried my best, this got pretty complicated over my head towards the end and I was never good at math to begin with. I was never bored thoughout this hit, and it was definitely one of the most interesting of any I have taken. ","I tried my best, this got pretty complicated over my head towards the end and I was never good at math to begin with. I was never bored throughout th is hit,  and it was definitely one of the most interesting of any I have taken. "],"rt":35033,"trial_type":"question","trial_index":0,"trial_index_global":87,"time_elapsed":2870626,"internal_chunk_id":"0-0.15-0"}]